douchebags.com 2017-11-27

# Douchebags™ Privacy Statement

This text is so private we have to share it with you.

{ Revised Date: October 6th, 2014 }

### WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS

We want you to feel safe online. For that reason, we want to let you know how we treat personal information that we collect from users of the Site, with a URL at www.douchebags.com (the “Site”). By providing personal information through the Site, you explicitly agree to our collection and use of all such information as described in this privacy policy.

### WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

We collect information from you when you order products on our Site. When ordering on our Site, you will be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, billing address, delivery address, phone number and, when making a purchase, credit card information. You may, however, visit our Site anonymously.

### WHAT DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To personalize your experience and improve customer service: Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs and more effectively respond to your customer service and support requests.  
To process transactions: Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the products you order from our Site. Your information may be shared with third party providers of credit card transaction processing services via the Pay Mill electronic commerce gateway. We also will share your contact information and address with our shipping partner to allow them to deliver your order to you.  
To send periodic emails: The email address you provide for order processing will be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. We may also email you about specials and promotions offered through our Site. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails from us, you may do so by following the detailed unsubscribe instructions included at the bottom of each email that you receive from us.  
All customers have the right to amend, access and delete their personal information as stated by the privacy ac. In order to do so, please contact us at: [privacy@douchebags.com](mailto:privacy@douchebags.com)

### HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

### COOKIES

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and understand and save your preferences for future visits. If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some aspects of our Site may not function properly.

### DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. However, when necessary we do share your information with trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, processing credit card transactions or otherwise conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

### CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our Site may make any changes to their information at any time by contacting us at [privacy@douchebags.com](mailto:privacy@douchebags.com). Please be sure to include your full name, address, e-mail address and specifically what type of information you do not want to receive. Please allow up to 6 to 8 weeks to process your request from the date of receipt. All customers have the right to amend, access and delete their personal information as stated by the privacy ac. In order to do so, please contact us at: [privacy@douchebags.com](mailto:privacy@douchebags.com)

### CHILDREN'S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE

In compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. In addition, we do not permit individuals who are under the age of 18 to purchase products on our Site. Our Site, products, and services are all directed to people who are at least 18 years old or older. If you under the age of 18, you should not use our Site or purchase any of our products from our Site.

### NEWSLETTER

We keep your personal information private, and will only use your email address to send you the newsletters you requested. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future newsletter from us, you may do so by following the detailed unsubscribe instructions included at the bottom of each email that you receive from us.

### LINKS TO OTHER SITES  

Our Site may contain links to other sites over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked sites may be different from our privacy policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policy at any site you visit.

### TERMS AND CONDITIONS

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our Site.

### CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

The use of your information is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time of use. We may amend this privacy policy from time to time. We post the current effective date of this policy at the top of the policy. Changes to the policy will be posted in the revised privacy policy with a new effective date on our Site. We encourage you to review our privacy policy periodically, because by visiting our Site you agree to accept any such changes.

### CONTACTING US

Please contact our privacy department at [privacy@douchebags.com](mailto:privacy@douchebags.com) if you have any questions.
